And the key thing to know for
关键是要知道
bag of words is that the word order does not matter.
词序并不重要
It's clearly a no, because we are counting words we have no preference to where in
这显然是一个不 因为我们计算的单词 我们没有偏好在哪里
the phrase a word occurs,
一个词出现的短语,
which kind of make it somewhat limited compared to really understanding a text.
与真正理解文本相比 这有点局限
It's kind of taking all the words and resorting them in random order.
这是一种把所有的单词随机排列的方式
That's why it's called bag of words.
这就是为什么它被称为词语袋
Because you toss them into a bag.
因为你把它们扔进袋子里
And gone they are.
他们都走了
Long phrases do give different vectors.
长词组确实给出了不同的矢量
So suppose we take the same email and duplicate it.
所以假设我们使用同一封邮件并复制它
All the counts go up by a factor of two, and
所有的计数都增加了两倍 而且
it's going to be a different input vector.
这将是一个不同的输入矢量
So to some extent you're biasing yourself to also encode the length of your text
所以在某种程度上 你是在偏向自己 以便同时编码文本的长度
not just the frequency of the words, so the answer would be clearly yes.
不仅仅是单词的频率 所以答案很明显是肯定的
And I would say, can we handle complex phrases.
我会说 我们能处理复杂的短语吗
Right now we can't, unless we make extra buckets for
现在我们不能 除非我们多做一些桶
those, which makes it a bit more difficult to preprocess.
这使得预处理变得更加困难
Chicago Bulls would count one for Chicago and one for Bulls.
芝加哥公牛队将为芝加哥公牛队计一分 公牛队计一分
And here's a funny little insight,
这里有一个有趣的观点,
when Google first came out as a search engine and you typed in Chicago Bulls.
当谷歌第一次出现作为一个搜索引擎 你在芝加哥公牛输入
You saw lots of, of, of references to cities and lots of references to animals.
你可以看到很多 很多关于城市和动物的参考资料
And so a, a bunch of smart Google engineers to change the dictionary to also
于是 一群聪明的谷歌工程师把字典也改成了
included combined phrases like Chicago Bulls.
包括像芝加哥公牛队这样的组合短语
So go to Google, try it out.
所以去谷歌上试试吧
I promise you you see very few animals and very few cities.
我向你保证 你看到的动物很少 城市也很少